freegrabapp.com 2019-12-16

# FreeGrabApp | Privacy Policy

By continuing to access and/or use any FreeGrabApp Site or Software following any update to this Privacy Policy, you are indicating and deemed to have agreed that you have read, understand, and agree to its updates and modifications and the entirety of the updated Privacy Policy.

### Our programs do not collect any kind of personal information

As you use any FreeGrabApp Software or Site, some information may also be collected passively, including your Internet protocol address, browser type, access time, mobile phone model, and telecom carrier. We may also store a "Cookie" on your computer or phone to store certain information about your use of any FreeGrabApp Software. We may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer or phone until you delete them). We may collect and store information locally on your device using mechanisms such as browser web storage and application data caches.

We may collect details of how you used any FreeGrabApp Software. We may share certain information with Google Analytics, for example. ([Google's privacy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy)).

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us by using this contact Email ([support@freegrabapp.com](mailto:support@freegrabapp.com)).
